

Haya Alajlan

Epidemiology graduate



Summary

A motivated Saudi young female holding a bachelor degree in Epidemiology with one year of internship at KFSHRC focused on research and analysis. Currently working as a volunteer researcher/analyst at Ministry of Health. Learned the different types of epidemiological studies, methods and sources of data, how the conduct and analysis of epidemiological studies works, the environmental health, toxicity health planning, biostatistics, and the application of ethical principles to research. Attended many courses and workshops.



Work History

2022-09 - Current

Data Analyst

Itkan Health Consulting

- Proposals writing.
- Data Analyzing using SPSS.
- Doing a literature reviews.

2022-05 -2022-08

Marketing Specialist

Abbott

- Marketing Diabetic devices, increased sales.
- Updated customer database and generated lists, counts and analysis for direct marketing projects.

2022-01 -2022-04

Technical Reviewer

TUV Rheinland Arabia

- Cooperation with Ministry of tourism to evaluate 5,000 facilities within 3
- Review reports by quality inspectors and write technical reports.

2021-09 -2021-12

Epidemiologist

Ministry Of Health

- Data analyzing using SPSS software.
- Create health survey guidelines for MOH.
 Working in sustainable development goals.

2019-09 -2020-08

Research Assistant

KESHRC

- Data analyzing using JMP and SPSS software.
- Search and doing studies.
- Use research results to write reports, papers and reviews and present findings in journals and conferences.
- Data collection and entry.



Education

2015-01 -2019-01

Bachelor of Epidemiology: Research

Princess Noura Bint Abdulrahman University - Saudi Arabia

• GPA: 4.43 out of 5.



Certifications

2018-08 1st Clinical Search Summer Course at KFMC

Research Road of Change Course at Almaarefa University 2018-06

2018-04 **SPSS**

20182 Application of Ethical Principles to Research and Public Health Practice

2020-04 **Biostatistics**

Mini MBA 2021-09



Address

Riyadh , SA, 12385

Phone

966-568-111667

E-mail

Haya.alajlan97@gmail.com

LinkedIn

http://linkedin.com/in/haya-alajlan-298a78157



Languages

Arabic: Native



English: Very good





Skills

Microsoft Office programs Excellent



SPSS software Excellent

JMP software



Excellent

Excellent

Data Analysis Excellent

Excellent



Research and studies Excellent



Communication Skills



Excellent

2021-09 Driving business towards the SDGs
2021-09 Business Management
2021-09 Risk Management
2022-09 Java Programming